Machine, I measure days by what I'd ever feeling, but that's it.
Please take a lantern. Sanitize your mirror.
This is not a real coat.
Our dental plan is tears of zine.
People start at 9 by 9.05. We've left space-time.
A wizard argues young with chatter.
Cryptid's microphone sounds bad.
A drive to just debate.
The neuter rupt for 40 consecutive minutes.
Feet, the shadow volume says hit delete.
Someone cries the earth is flat.
Someone else has proved the cat, the Jecto machine
Proof, wonder, yelled at glowing
The library has every text
But nobody knows which book is next
The rituals are strictly voluntary
Except returning books to the library
Music absolutely slaps so sing
And your application to become supreme assistant deputy junior lantern
Thank you so much. Yeah, I did a couple I did a few cool video. Oh, okay. I have my closer
Hold me fix my my green screen a little bit that off. Yeah, that works. Okay. Hi
What's up, thank you so much case 300 glow come back. Um, he came up during the middle of that. Um, you know
I will say he did call me today and was like I'm five minutes away and I was you know I
cleaned my house as best I could and um I fucking got out the fan and I was I'm glad to say I was
so disgusting and sweaty still but I was about to I was about to uh open the door he said he's
bringing pizza a beer I go to my phone he's like I'm not gonna come what a cock dude come on 300
I think he was getting drunk and having fun with his wife or whatever and you know, that's always important. Yeah for real
It's okay. Yeah, it's for real. Yeah, I was gonna like stream with them and stuff
It was gonna be so much fun, but you know what? He will come back
I'm sure he was like literally five minutes away, but I don't have a car
So it was like we'll come to my place because I'll take me like half hour to walk over there
So if I need to clean my place, but um
He's like, okay, we'll go over there and then
So workout, but it will work out next time. I'm sure it will work out
Okay, I finished my coffee and put it on my glass.
It does suck.
Because I wanted it to meet 300 blow and I was so excited.
We were talking on the phone.
But you know what he said?
He said he loves me.
That's a freaking progress somewhere around there.
Well, I just as a friend, I'm sure.
Anything weird?
Okay, Lenore was just inside.
I think she ran back.
It's really, it is like hot today.
I mean, tell me how it is.
What time is it?
It's like nine, or it's 10.30 and it is 80 degrees inside here.
So it is warm here.
It's a little bit warm.
Okay.
Oh.
So how was your day? I actually so go if you weren't here earlier tripping tripped and simp I call him
That's his new nickname. Okay. Everyone else can call him that from now on trip and simp. Thank you so much
Trimpet trip and simp
Well, the other day on be this told me to go if you wanted my address so he'd send me a rope so I could hang myself
Okay, and I was like wow that doesn't seem very character- I didn't know he was like such a like a fucking mean person
But I didn't do anything. I just asked him for I said, okay
You just like put out a show to your your syndication
And he's like, oh just because you asked I'm not gonna do it. He hates me. I guess cuz I think he's like a big
Kate Kate's turtle butt liquor. He's just like get a night when Q came in and formed on me. So then this today
Trip and simp came in
And he started saying the n-word over and over again, so I banned him.
And then he's like, oh, I was just kidding.
Can you unban me?
Stupid me.
I was like, okay.
I mean, it's like, I don't know.
I was just like, well, there's no way.
And he's just kidding.
Maybe he's just like, you know, ahead of the lapse in judgment or something.
So I unban him.
He comes up and he does it again, okay?
And then guess what?
Then I then he's like well, um, I was gonna tell you something really cool. Can I come back again? As you know?
It's okay. I mean fool me fool me once shame on me fool me or fool me once shame on you
Should pull me twice shame on me, right?
And then Kate was in the chat saying oh, but he was gonna tell you a real cool thing of gossip
But not anymore and now we're not gonna tell you
Well, what fucking, I mean, who cares?
What kind of gossip could be good enough to, you know,
to risk my channel to have this jerk come up twice,
say the N word a bunch of times?
So I went to Case Chat and I was like,
hey, Kate, can you tell Q and Tripp and Sip,
who you're probably paying to like harass my show
and n-bomb me and forebomb me?
Can you just stop doing that?
Cause I don't fuck with your show,
so don't fuck with my show.
I said that on the left.
So we'll see how that goes,
Q is up there and stuff.
I mean...
I don't go to places and just start attacking randomly.
I mean, it's like, I was in, like, Sandman's head today,
but, you know, that Lady Bazzard band's every account.
Beat is in there.
talking about my cats and saying,
oh, three cats have run away in a year.
Look, look, look, look, look, look.
First of all, this has been two years, you know,
it's like a second of all,
would you want me to have like nine cats?
I don't understand.
They want me to have nine cats or something like that.
That's what they want.
I couldn't be able to handle nine cats, I don't think.
I can only handle them before
because the five of them were little kittens.
When they got bigger,
it gets a little crowded in here, okay?
So, you know, cats wander.
Someone said oh your cats eat a lot of the coyotes have eaten all your cats
No, I find one of my cats got by a coyote before even started doing my show y'all peep the boo boo at damn poppies
KT
But what does that mean? I don't know. What is boo boo the shit at?
What is what is dump? What is dumb poppies? Hey Mason? What's up? Man are we so cool as long as you brought the pizza
You brought the pizza, right? Did you bring the pizza?
Mason, I'll tell you
It was be paid for right you didn't send me to that piece of that night more. It's a big scandal now, but it's in your thoughts
It's a much trouble. I'm just kidding. Yes. I love you Mason. Do you want to come up? I'll put my link up
There we go. We are still cool Mason
Long as you bring the pizza and your good attitude your good positive attitude. I love it
So wow guys look at my apartment. We can really see it, but I did like clean the fuck
Heck out of it today. Boo-boo ain't no poo-poo-foo. Who's boo-boo? Are you talking about boo-boo kitty? Are you boo-boo kitty, Tete?
Hey man, see how are you sweetheart?
Boo-boo ain't no poo-poo-foo-foo.
Yeah, she is. She's sweet poo. Or sour poo. I don't know.
Imagine somebody eats like a big thing of
sour jolly ranchers and poops. That's sweet pea. That's about as much as I like sweet pea.
I'm sorry, because it's graphic.
Okay.
Yeah, I moved my couch out of the way.
I mean, or it's kind of like the,
the, I'll show you a second to see what it did.
So this was like up against my,
I changed things around a little bit.
Just take this off for you to go.
Okay, so let me check it out, check it out,
or see, there, I put that in from there, see?
It's kind of like that. It's not perfect. It's like the blanket's on, so, but see, and I got everything in the pre-organized, even the floors, like, kind of, oh, gosh, I know it's like, you know, it's like, you know, I don't, they need to give me just black carpet, I mean, just black carpet so you don't see, I mean, I do, like, walk around in my apartment a lot, you know, it's like, I was supposed to get, also, Harvard floors, and literally, at one point, that was, like, from my former brother-in-law, I promise it was, but he,
The worst my sister so you'd like some pizza if you can get some cheese sticks. Well, you know what?
We have a cheese steak factory or cheese cake factory in five minutes walking distance
So you want to come on a cheese cake factory? You want to be on the phone with you be on the phone with Christine?
What are you talking about sleepy?
Yes, I really want you to come up Mason get up here. It's your oh here. He is there's Mason the drummers in the check
No, I'm just you know, but I did I used to have your pick. I had one of your pictures on my last
He was trying to get video of you, but I ran out of credits
But all the be you'll be in that in that uh, the thing that is video soon come on up
I mean it's like Christine be there they just had that all they do is want to just talk shit about me
I mean if they don't understand so yeah, I mean and then I'll react of course, but it's like
What I've said and something like that is nothing in comparison to the shit. They're saying
Tata is sweet pea. I think Nancy she's sweet pea
Or else he's that terrible exiled one's,
not exiled one, what's his name?
Pashaki?
Hold on, let's see, what's the guy's name?
Not exiled one, what is it?
Anything that is, I think that was,
it's the guy with the pie, he has pie as his,
maybe it is exiled one, it's not complete.
Remember that I had this really dorky British guy on today,
he was really, I'm kind of spun.
Oh, that's your bakelips. You're always saying I was when you know what happened
I ran out of weed and so I'm really hyper but I'm gonna ban you again if you keep saying shit like that thing that was
Bakelips that was about that
Yeah, it's not the real thing that is it's just um
It's his it's one of his it's his brother that was born first and then there's also the brother thing that could be
The thing that could be I know but I know it's you bake lips and you keep saying shit like that
And I don't like it imagine if you're like a comedian on the stage and then someone's like hey
You're on meth and then I just like kind of just takes the whole mood of the whole whole
showdown and then I'm gonna have to call security and you know I
Don't have to do that say hell. Yes. Hell. Yeah, my kid is
So funny. Okay, well, you know what there's a clown that wants to perform some dental surgery on you
I'm sure he'll love your your jokes go in there and talk to him
Okay, his name is his name is Leroy
Okay. Oh my gosh. I'm gonna wear my
So I thought I found this I didn't remember some of the things I bought but look this is a beautiful
It's called a mala necklace. These are beads. They're beautiful. These are green beads
They kind of go with my goddess. I have a speedo on right now. No, I'm not wearing underwear
I think the speed is almost dry though. I can fit it on a few
So what am I doing?
I don't know, it's considering like maybe like,
doing something like, you know,
if somebody wants to like, watch me cut all my hair off,
I can like, you know,
they can do like $5 and I'll do just for like each $5.
And then the only rule is I'll leave it how it is
until the end of the show.
But then after the show, I can shave it all off
because I don't want to look stupid.
Okay.
Well, I can try. I'm just thinking and throwing ideas out there. I mean, it's what what it's Kate and Sam and
Looking sane on me. Yeah, I used to get I used to shave my head sometimes
And whenever I did I'd start getting like pulled over by the police because they thought I was like some kind of criminal
I mean, I look I look scary with it. I do I look so kind of scary with that. I had to I don't look as nice
And so I get pulled over. Oh my gosh. Yeah, so I do kind of like my long hair like this, but
It would be a tension, I know, but if we talk about it,
they just need to donate about it.
So here's my thing.
Let's just do, and I'll get on my,
I have electric razor and stuff here.
I can put in my cash app if you wanna.
I don't know if Alex will be here.
I think Alex and I are like on more of a truce energy
right now, which I'm, you know,
I always prefer peace over conflict, you know?
I just want to keep it cool.
Here's my cash up if anyone wants to support the uh,
I need to, actually, yeah, yeah, this will work.
And then I could maybe refute from my phone bill
and stuff, I mean, gee, hey, look at this, rise up.
There I am.
It's that blue glow about me.
Define truths, cause I don't, yeah, okay.
I mean, it's like, you know, it's fine,
but she privateed those videos.
I know, it's like, and then, let's just say,
I mean, I just I'm just happy to have a truth. She thinks I'm like I'm like I'm turning into a wolf or something like that
I'm not quite sure how how what the story is where the McDonald's fries this time back take you along with my jar jar
Big shirt. Where is it? I don't know
Joker said it's on site. What's on site?
They didn't give me a kiss. It's so hard for oh, I know. Well, it's you know, it's fine
But I think she's like now. She's kind of she's talking more about Rick. I am next
pebbles and
and Zeya. I wasn't mentioned the last time I listened so I think it's progress but you know okay
you know it's uh not amusing but the extreme a bit is funny I know I mean I kind of like extremes
Joker said I'm creepy you wouldn't say that Joker was creepy to me
until yeah no I mean I think you know listen it's like you know we're at the
end of the day it's a show it's entertaining like that's I want to
entertain she told me do the mean degree at the show and I told her that it's
like you know just take it as entertainment I guess you know it's
like who even knows maybe it was all it's a charade that we did just for
For ratings we was just a rating stuff. I just imagine that Joker's done with me pack myself up
I just said hi to Joker like you know
Earlier, he didn't seem to say anything like that
Sandman talks like that pack yourself up
You just give yourself away, and you didn't even spell yourself right? Y-A-S-E-L-F. It's not you spell yourself
It's like it's some it's like a Hebrew name. Yes, yes, sir. Oh, really?
Does that mean that they got Palestine? Yes, sir. They are fat. I'm sure okay. Well
Well, while we're waiting for someone to okay, so let me see. I'll do my I'll see you my other
awesome amazing
lovable
incredible
So night
And so cast a shadow every shadow welcome
There's hello John. I mean, uh, psyche. Hello
I didn't I didn't okay. I fucked up. I've been here that fucking
Every day for fucking 40 days. I've been here that fucking name. I had to slip. I'm sorry, man
Well, I've been I've been calling you god and god for at least a year. We'll keep going man. It's good. It's working
I'm afraid of it too. I got fucking worshipers and everything. I guess fucking going great
I'm gonna start a new religion. Can I just call you Benjamin or Mark or whatever?
Go ahead. You're a good friend. You can do it, man. I want to call you Ben
You've always been good to me. Just don't call me bent over, huh? Okay. I won't I'm not
I'll never ask you to grab your ankles and never never never no no no no it's not like that kind of show
I dropped the link in the back if you don't mind playing. Oh my god. We've got a new gotty song
It's my fucking world premiere pal got it. I get the exclusive. Yes, you do buddy
minutes long you don't have to play nine minutes only five minutes that's all
you gotta do is five minutes okay fuck it it's the book it's the book baby it's
the book but the five ugly animals I saw that no no no no no no no no that's
different this is the book this is my real book coming out in October this is
the preview baby but I just want to say Goddy you know some of the animals were
not the best looking animals but the monkey was cute
The monkey. Yeah, usually the monkey is the cute one. Yeah, but this one this one is totally different. This is the book
Cyber Satan and the coming of the digital apocalypse. Oh, this is so exciting cyber get it and enjoy everyone
Yes, exactly just for you go ahead and enjoy
I think fuck yourself
Has fallen, the commons been foretold
Side forget is calling, revelations to point
Your soul belongs to the code
That's not me, that's flirty
Thanks bro, you like that shit, huh?
Yeah, you can shut it off, awesome
I gotta do a deep connect
Thanks bro
Yeah, that's the book basically, come to you know
Little preview of the book
How everything's gonna go down but look at Mason's hitting on reality Nancy again
He's calling her my love look at Mason's a fucking horn dog
Huh, and then big clips now and big clips once I make out with Mason's these cities a funny troll big clips and Mason
That's a different dynamic. I haven't seen that day in May. That's a cute. Yeah, there you go. They may maybe maybe
Yeah, even better. Yeah
Nice Mason you've got a date with a guy and perhaps really Mason's a fucking pimp
Mason's a pimp. That's what they should call him not the drummer Mason the pimp. You should call him pimp the drummer shit
Look at you. He was Chanel's into it. It's called Mason sticks from now on just sticks
This is a big sticks Mason. We got to get you a velvet suit. How about that?
A velvet suit. Oh my gosh, you know, I'm wearing a velvet cape in my my ladies. You saw the newest intro, right?
Yeah, that was good with the one with the lantern
Well, no, that was that was that's another one, but I made a funny one like with trolls in it and stuff
Oh, no, I didn't see that one
Yeah, yeah play it play. I got two minutes. Okay. Thank you. I think you like this
Thanks for playing that by the way
Please take a lantern sanitize your mirror and remember
This is not a real cult.
It's not?
Our dental plan is terrible.
Walk out, walk out.
Hey, who's you?
Which one?
The Wizard?
Oh, f**k, cool.
The Wizard.
Okay, I'll go.
Joe the Blade, the first gate.
Oh, let's go.
The Sphinx said, buddy,
that's confirmation by
a cult master, Warraville,
and you're to escape.
Look at the clown, that's the thing.
He shouted, Traveler, set me free.
Oh my god
What do you do fucking dress yourself
I
What did you do? What did you do? Squirt all over your face?
What if I kept blacked out in your house boy?
Because you would be there to guard you.
Hey Rosita, chill out will ya?
Nobody's talking to you.
I wouldn't want your wife to kill me.
I mean, I think she now speaks to everybody and says,
eww.
El grosso, el grosito.
I throw myself.
Yo quiero Taco Bell.
I used to say gross in Mexican.
Grosita.
Cochino, Cochino.
So what's up, psyche?
What's up?
Look at this.
Fuck it.
He looks like a Mexican Dracula.
Doesn't he look like a greasy Mexican?
I was going to wear a thong for you were I would love that tonight or on the show tonight are you doing the show I'll put my
I want to wear a badass thong for you. Okay
Why not we can we can get matching speedos on the beach someday if you want to come to them
We're in the beach for why I can't wear a badass thong for you
Of course you can, but we had I mean it's like I don't know if you want that all
Yes, yes you can
You know
We're just going home we're not going over to that
Hey, but do you hear him straight now?
Nigger, nigger, nigger, nigger.
Oh my god.
Dina, can you say that on the show?
She was saying vinegar?
No, it's nice and weird shit.
Oh my god.
Why is it that my, why is it my fault?
I don't know, but hey, I'm hypnotized by your kids right now.
We're right next to each other, right?
I know, I can almost feel you from where, you know, almost.
I can't wear a thong for you or what?
You can't, but shh, we'll do it in private.
Don't tell nobody, don't tell nobody.
I mean, no one knows, no one will know.
I'm aware of how that's thong for you.
Hell yeah.
All right, get a Mexico one.
Don't tell nobody, at least one.
Get a Mexico one and I'll go south of the border
and liberate it from Mexico.
Yeah, and Dina's going to suck my dick at the same time.
She's about to die.
Wow.
OK, well.
Oh!
I don't think it's a yes. I mean
Oh my god
Yeah, no one's gonna tell but there's just oh, there's only 19 people in the room. I'm not down. Do you where I?
Don't have a thought I have an American flag speeder that I just pulled my butt cheeks a little bit in the back
Okay, okay, well next time I'll have it for you
You all do you want to get I'll get out how about you get a US when I'll get a Mexico one. I got a badass down
You got a fat ass ass.
I got a badass ass and a thong.
I don't even wear a thong.
Yeah, only if you do.
And she has to wear bikini and we all have to go to the beach.
She's okay with it.
Okay, and she's the coolest wife in the world.
I love it.
We're nice to you. We're nice to you.
I know, and next time, you have to come next time.
When are you coming back to Redondo?
You're at the pier.
I told you to pull up, bro.
I was going to, but then I was like, okay, well,
it was like half hour away to walk,
and then I needed to clean my house
so you could be like presentable for you,
because I didn't want you to think
I'm some kind of-
Did you have a nice bang on bag?
Yeah, do you want me to put it on?
I can put it on right now.
Let me see it.
Okay. Let me find it. I need to get it. I'm gonna do it for you. Okay. Okay. Let's do it together.
Since everybody's taking this funny, let's do it together.
Oh, here we found it. I mean, it's gonna change. Oh my gosh, I'm a little bit
You should go to Redondo Beach and knock that nigger psyche out.
Oh my god.
That's actually sexy.
Oh shit.
Oh, you're sexy.
Thank you.
That ass is sexy.
Hey, hold on.
I can do better.
Let me see.
That's sexy.
Psyche, what are you going to do when I eat your ass?
Relax.
I've probably had an orgasm.
I don't know.
You're gonna let me your ass or no absolutely absolutely, and I'm not gonna get jealous
I'm just eating not either
We're gonna have it's over the way. Hey, we're gonna really we're having salads. We're all gonna have salads together
Not a respect to sex
Well, oh my gosh, there's noble Castro. Hey, you're a noble Castro. He's a he's a Hispanic
Hey, what if I wear a pink thong for you?
Oh, you have one? I thought you were wearing wear it right now. Now I'm all upset.
I have pink thong for you.
Okay, put it on. I'm gonna take me stand up. I want to see what you're wearing.
You think I'm gonna look sexy?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yes or no?
I love a little bit.
What if I wear a pink thong right now?
I didn't trust in my ass.
Yeah, Noble Caster needs to smoke.
I wish I had, I mean, I'm out of weed now, isn't that terrible, but yeah.
What'd you walk into? I don't know, you just walked into the best show.
Oh my God.
I don't welcome you. Yes.
It's a welcome. It's a good American welcome. It's a welcome to America.
Are you gonna like me wearing a pink thong?
Yes. Hot pink.
Pissed my ass.
Yeah.
What would you...
Hell yes.
Yeah, I'll put this to your ass right now too.
Gosh, I wish we would've come over now. We would've had so much fun.
I wish we should've met.
Stupid fucking cock-cumper. Bag it, nigger.
Look at my...
If he plays another AI video, I'm gonna neck.
My chat said they wanna kill each other.
Oh, that's your chat.
I thought Dino was saying terrible things to me.
You thought 300 blow you a fucking asshole.
My chat said they're down to kill you.
Oh my God, I love, I have a murder cut.
Hey, can I kill you?
Can I cut your head off?
Only if you have your tongue down my throat at the time,
then I won't kill you.
Why can I kill you?
If you have one thing in my butt
and then one tongue down my throat,
then you can chop my head off.
And then I can kill you?
Yeah, I mean, I'll die happy.
Why not?
My gosh, I didn't have sex with my corpse like that. Can I kill you? Yes, you know
Yes, I'm gonna choke you out with my dick. Okay
You're gonna like it. Mm-hmm. I mean, just don't like maybe really die
I just want to be respectful be with you. I will I will
Don't be mine and dine him. I mean, why did she say factory if he wants to go and I choke you with my dick? Yes
Love it. I want to like I like it when I'm almost I think I'm gonna die and then I like I
Go I think that and I'm back to life. Yeah, but I'm not gonna kill you. Thank you. Perfect. I think I think it's perfect
Hey, you suck my dick
Like like an uber vacuum, you know cleans the floor because I have Dina Dina said like as long as they protect you
She's okay with it. Wait. I need to wear a dental dam or you're gonna wear a column. She said as long as you suck my day
Okay, okay
Yes
You know how to suck it. Hell, yes, I'll give her some tip. I'll teach her how to do it better because women sometimes they don't
Passed out
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you
100% I'm straight. I know you are. I know so my day. I like that even better and I
Don't even care if I had my head. It's hot. I'll get the hole. I'll get it. I'll get it all in there
You'll finish me off
Whatever you want, baby. Oh, yeah, that's how it is, right? Yep
So what? There's things like you don't suck me ever finish me out
You know how to suck a race like you
Yeah, yeah, I
Can go real
Do my eyes water and like mucus starts coming out of my nose. All right, I'll see you later
I'm gonna go talk to my girl. Okay. Let her let her know where we're going. We're like two minutes away. It's y'all know
Yes, see get over here on the way
But if she doesn't suck it you're gonna suck it good for me. Of course
Well, I don't tell everybody. Okay. I won't tell anybody. I mean we're out on the air
I'll see you later my boy
Love you, baby
Who's your daddy? Who's your daddy?
I
And then I love
Alexander and then shot this head off. I like Alexander my I like everybody
I like I like you sweetheart. You're all lower gay as hell
So cute. Oh, it's so cute
Yeah, so my chat said it kicked you out. Okay. Can you keep me out?
I'll see you later, bro.
I love you, baby.
Bro, we have our own phone person now.
I know, call me.
I have the American phone.
Don't tell nobody, don't tell nobody.
I'm not gonna snitch.
I am.
If you want to see the red,
was under the American flag.
Are you gonna snitch on my personal phone?
No, of course not.
Hey, it's called Silencio.
It's called the Law of Silencio.
I'm not gonna dodge you, psyche.
Don't do that.
I'm not gonna dox you either do that. I'm not gonna dox you. I like you, bro
I'm not gonna put the address
Thank you. Well, it's already out there, but it's a it's fine. I would never do that
Well, I'll say you better not do that for them. Okay before you go. Can you give me a quick flex and stand up?
What you want? Yeah, baby. Oh, yeah, there we go. Yeah. Oh, it's
Hey, you're a real man. I love you
Shout out to you psyche. I love you, bro. Okay. Thank you
Take care, bro
Listen to me soon. I really love you, bro. I love you too. No, I really love you, bro
I really love you and I'll prove it to you when I see you
I
Make you happy. Okay. No, I'm happy. You're fair man. I'm happy no matter what. Oh, you're police not
Hey, make it a merry Christmas for me make it a really
I'll stop. I'll stop. Hey, you're so sexy. I love you. I love you, bro. I love you more
I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you more. I love you
I don't care bro. I don't care either. I call it I call it red bull. I love you bro. I love you too sweetie. Okay, I'll talk to you soon.
See you later bro. You're cat high. You're so concrete. Wow. I think I got a date guys. Wow. Okay, well let's forget about the I'm Street thing. Let's just say, let's just say I'm bisexual. Because I would totally have nice Mexican food like that.
Whew, what, why am I just so hot all of a sudden?
Ooh, wow, guys.
Oh, I mean, gosh, I'm so sorry.
I know that was a little bit much.
We finally scared baked lips away.
I don't think baked lips has ever been scared away.
Syrup wizardry, I like your names.
Syrup, like, what kind of syrup?
Like, is that like lean or is it like,
you know, hanjima's buttery syrup?
Maybe that's what he's oiled up on, I don't know.
All I know, I think I'm in love.
I think I'm in love.
Hey, I mean, I do it as a really funny,
do you wanna see if I can find like 300
of those first appearance on my show?
Let me fix my, there we go.
Oh, okay.
So, let me see if I can find my first appearance
or his first appearance on the codex.
Let's see.
I search for 300 glow.
Okay, here he is.
Go 300 glow.
Okay.
Um, oh, there's a long pair of them. Okay, so it says this. Um, let's see. So this is, um
Friendly rail here he is
Okay, hold on. He's gonna be in this episode with sick here. We're gonna work back to the past bang bang
That's anything I say
Yeah, he dry snitched
Okay, here we go
Oh, okay, so you guys know sure on to look how drunk I am
Easy easy. You want to ban him
I got 50 hours for a lifetime ban from my channel.
Easy one.
And then you're nervous.
That's how you finally get nervous.
My jambles.
How drunk am I?
Oh my god.
I never even do this drunk anymore.
Jambles?
That's good.
Go ahead.
Elaborate sake.
You're very, very cryptic.
He's going to be, okay.
He's going to be annoying.
I said I can't take any more of him.
He can't.
Yeah.
He drives the opposite way down the road and kills everybody.
You're going to drive like you fucking drunk asshole.
There you go.
300 glow.
I mean, I don't know.
300.
I give you the link to my shit.
I guess you left me.
Oh, watch your kissing.
Say it.
300 glow said that 300 glow said that psyche is backstage spreading his asshole. Oh my god
He's still less gay than 300 low even a slice backstage pregnancy, so he's still less gay than 300 low. Thank you very much
There's 300 stand for the number of dick shoes like socks 300 though, or is that just like a name?
I just wondering sir. That's not very well. Let's see
That's crazy
That's cool. That's gaysy
Patrick's wayzy
Brazy
Well, I think I love about saying is that he has nine tits. That's a real fucking man right there
Oh, hello. 300 glow said that he's going to fuck your face. Joe. How do you feel about that?
Wow.
Better not.
Who would say to another guy want to fuck your face? Oh, a gay guy would.
300 glow said that.
I don't believe it.
I know that's what I'm saying. 300 glow is gay.
and some hair. You wish you had hair like that, SIG.
Is he a glow?
He said he didn't wash up late at his wife, and then I went backstage and I showed my dick.
And you saw my dick, SIG. You saw my dick, right?
Oh, hold on a second.
Hold on a second. Who's this? Who's this?
Wait, are you here? Are you back?
I heard somebody, I heard somebody was looking for me.
I was.
Hey.
Hey Papi.
What's up?
What's up dude?
I
I do apologize if I did anything wrong
I get drunk and I like hit on guys
Hey no worries
I didn't want to offend you. Okay. I heard you were looking for me. So I got I was I got real
You were your roof and I was looking for you. I'll leave you. You're so cute. You get that you get that
That's great
It's crazy. You get a cute face
crazy
I don't have the the neck beard like signal. I'm sorry
Since this thing revenge
See six to be using your grandmother, you know, it says there. Yeah, I think it's like dress like my grandma every day
I just want my six boot range that night. That's crazy
I don't walk around naked all the time.
My day is pretty good.
My girl is drinking.
We're all drinking for Cinco de Mayo.
Hey, have a good day, Mayo.
Nice watch
What you said and we're cashing in my show you really
I I said jiggers
You say
I said I said sick titties jiggle
Okay, okay. Okay. I won't do it again. Well, psyche psyche wants to end the stream. So you guys have a freak off again
You're
We were sure about holes and then
Rage
He was playing with his beard while just watch
Yeah
What with one hand and
Me
That's crazy
Getting the shirt off. I told you I buy you one
Yes
I wouldn't do anything with him if she said wait up guys. I'm arguing with my wife. She's in charge. She's in charge of them
Pay attention
I'm talking to you. He's on a
real quick. Hey, shout out to
the next up and coming
streamer. He's going to blow
up and he's going to blow
everybody off. You know it.
Maybe. Maybe. I heard you better
before, but I'm like 11 viewers
I'm working on it. I'm working on it. Can you do the foot thing? Can you show your bottom of your shoe?
Oh, hell, so much.
I need to make this punk right now.
Say, I just want to talk to him for a second.
When I hear a point, I just want to say that I...
Yeah, you do the...
He left. He left when I kicked him off.
Okay, never mind. See.
Why did you kick him off?
I didn't came out he left
I think you guys were hitting it off very well
I know
They see you at Benny Blanco's earlier in my screen. We're Benny Blanco's earlier
I definitely saw people some people in the chat that I knew yeah, dude 300 you're on my stream. Why did you leave?
This is like lat over a year ago. This is when I started streaming
I'm gonna like oh, it looks so terrible. This is like this is like when I took that second picture
I mean, I was just like, you know, I was just drunk and
Terrible my little man a scale of 100 to 100. Well a scale of 100 to 100 with being like
There's no other option besides 100
Say I think yours. I think your sex appeal needs to be raised a little bit
I think you need to like flex for the camera
So you're like you're just like other way
No, we're you flex what it's just flex one time as well. He's one time
Bands you just flex flex get it get him out of there. No, you're not going to
Time oh, I don't want to see
Yeah, bye. Bye see I'll see you next time. I'll see you next time. See you another day
Okay, I just can't take it guys you leave me alone with sick
There's no donations. No no cash app. No readings. Just leave me alone with sick
I know you guys are disgusting. It's really disgusting. No one even donated for my hair be cut tonight
Oh
Is he back
You muted me before you even thought I'd hear you asshole and I came up because you don't want to be by yourself
Hey, listen, what are you doing now you look like you're stressed out and wasted he looks like he's having a really good time
I'm always good
Well, what are based my liver probably could be work on yet. I've got literally like one
If that
Fucking real boozy
What
Joe's ass
You have your ass
Oh no, I just spilled my coffee.
Okay, I will be right back.
I just spilled my drink all over my floor.
And you know what, that's what I get.
That's what karma is for me being a melty little thing,
you know?
Yeah, you could have paid, just not karma.
That's actually, just don't have to.
Oops, I did it again.
Oh, whoops, I spilled a beer again, I cheated it.
Yeah, it's good 2007, 2008, 2009 fucking Britney Spears.
Yeah, it's a good fight on an album yesterday.
I think Britney will sing Britney.
I don't know, it brings a twin.
Well, you can sing whatever you want, but like, I was just saying.
Remember that one time when the guy's like stop attacking bread. Hey
But she's lost her fucking mind
In that ensemble on the internet with knives, I hope one of you
Okay, let's make you a most biggest celebrity. Let's make it. Let's say
Let's make some YouTube stars
Let's make let me be a son and create all these stars in the sky all these YouTube stars
like what 40, 50, 70, 100, a thousand dollars.
How about like 100 million dollars, like Dr. People says?
Yeah.
And Joe, Joe, how much is the jock strap you're wrestling in when you're like 25 years old?
The jock strap, how much is the jock strap?
He's going off about it still you guys listen to him ever like I've been actually listening to him lately like when he's talking
He's going off. He's just a freak
Look at it says
Who do you think you're hot shit like you think you're hot legs like Rod Stewart. You ain't fucking Rod Stewart
You should start selling your I don't know. Oh, yeah, that's something
Shit the jug
You wouldn't buy by the throat of my neighbor that I don't like
That seems like such a process you could just not
It looks like it came from a guy that looks like Johnny debt
There you go pose. There you go. Oh my god. What am I doing? There you are. He's tired, little sexy pose, little tired pose. I don't, I don't feel, I don't feel like I'm doing this stuff.
That's your page, poach. You have to like not look like you're dead or that you've got D. You gotta look coherent, right? Cause else it's not good for anybody.
It's like you remind me of the guy from you, you remind me of you, you know what it's like
from you.
I love you man.
I can't love psych.
It was so funny.
Fuck, are any of us gonna go to bed ever?
I think I just went to bed.
Probably should.
I'm gonna sleep right away.
I'm so tired I don't even know how I'm still...
You're a loser. You could never handle me.
Anyway, I'm pretty tired. Let me just go to sleep, guys.
I just left her alone with you.
I would say Psych Awakens. He's a mystical bean.
That's a mystical bean. You want to talk about a mystical man?
You look at that
No, I just think that one of the eyes is just like like trying to like go in more than the other one
But it's not cross-eyed or I do that too. You're looking into the camera Joe. It's normal. Oh
See you know lacrosse like that, but when you're like trying to look into the camera, okay, I mean that's enough of that
Let me see, this one says, I mean, Night Madness.
I think he might be on this one.
Let me check this out, let me see.
Okay, this one's a little bit longer, let me see.
Oh, he is, okay.
Your soul belongs to me now.
Oh, my soul doesn't belong to me, please.
Your soul is all mine.
Can you suck it up, like in one, one goal?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I'd love to see that.
Hey, we have sick here to say hi to you too.
Do they sick?
Do you think it's sick?
Oh yeah, sick's the best.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, signal.
Oh, he's one of my favorites this guy.
This guy's the best.
Yo.
You know psyche this guy 300 glow wants you to let him on would you let him on of course glow
This guy's the best.
Yo.
300 is saying that you should wear a wife beater
This guy's the best.
All right, he's switching into his outfit. It's like we're in a green fez
It looks like I can't see your face or what you're wearing
Hmm
God is wearing like a
Is it like a bag full of Goddy? It looks like it looks like actually
Goddy it looks like our excuse me God
Looks like
Somebody that's hiding worse. Yeah, all your heart wheels. They you're bald
Don't make this shit up. It's okay. I love it. You don't make shit worth more money than your balls. Nega
I got a
Exit in some more war. I have one motorcycle. That's more worth more than all your heart wheels nigger
But yes, I know
750s nigger
Your motorcycle in a hot wheel
Let's see worth more than you're
Stupid
Sucker
If you're stuck in dick here, it's like he's the best per verb
I'll go second.
One retry at a time.
Oh my god.
Signal.
You ain't gonna like those signals, Dick, when you sucking it.
So he goes last for sure.
Yeah, well, it's probably the size of a pacifier.
And so I'm not really interested.
I don't want to swear and glow.
Like, I just want to like...
Oh, shit.
...to beat his arms.
What does it call it? Los Monos?
Yeah, like this one.
Oh, man.
Yes.
Here's mama. Hey, I'm really from Jalisco, Guadalajara, Mexico. I'm from
Santa Muerte
That's what we believe in Santa Muerte
You are hey stop saying that name
she told me what i said
hey uh psyche you have a lot of negative energy talking on the the devil on like the
santa muerte coming to you
okay first of all she said stop calling her the devil she doesn't like being called the devil
that's bad luck that's bad luck
santa muerte coming for you
yeah i'm worried to talk to me i've talked to like this expansion
okay i see
you can think of other things that are bad luck
You said it was nothing. You said it was a finger.
in my mouth
now
let's eat
but
for my wife
it's blue
it means red
it means blue
it means green
and amoreo means yellow
congratulations buddy
typical faipanol english
FANTASMA!
One point.
My English?
J.D.
It's FANTASMA.
Hey, you know where all the white boys from Waila, how'd that come from?
From me?
Yeah.
I'm that bloodline.
It's FANTASMA.
Yeah, because J.D. and I are, I think by, like,
hey, Psyche, I even look whiter than you, maybe.
It's FANTASMA.
I'm from, I'm from, why do I look whiter than you?
I see kids are racist against white people.
I think white people are too dark.
They're like, oh, they're like, oh, they're like,
why white people?
People are too pink.
They're Diablo, Blanco, Blanco is Diablo.
We are too pink.
Blanco is Diablo.
I don't even know pink in the white people have high blood pressure. Thanks to your
Drinking vodka
Why hey, you're you remember we're seeing that McDonald's movie
Where the white boy eats ten McDonald's murk fucking Big Mac's
Yes, I love pressure
And I'm over here buying corn and tacos, nothing but surreal food.
Tacos, locals.
Who's gonna help live you?
It's not a taco truck.
It's a white training.
The two buying McDonald's every day, or the two buying tacos every day for the corner.
They're both in the jungle that look healthier.
They're both high in cholesterol.
Okay, I
Was I've been a part of iarta and they take you into the jungle is literally the jungle and then there's people living there
You're like, what the fuck is going on?
In America why you guys all sitting down you guys been sitting down all day already why you guys sit down for
I want you guys want to check out where it was.
Yeah, I did.
Why does everyone sit down?
Yeah, everyone get up.
Y'all sit down around all day for hours.
Bro, your backs are going to blow out.
Y'all going to stand up for a little bit
and your back going to blow out.
I like you to stand up because I can see your butt
and then...
Happy oh, yeah, that's what you like for show psyche and I'ma show you
Hey psyche you send me send me a hundred and I got you
But it has to be personal you can't upload it you ever been to Africa dog
Why the fuck would I go to Africa of our Mexican? Have you ever been to Africa? I'm Mexican so what what do you mean so what?
My ancestors in Mexican and Aracha, why would I go to Africa? That's not my that's not where my generation is from
jungle in Mexico
What do you mean, let's see let's see
Kick them out
You're a racist, but I don't care, I don't care, like, bitches, bruh.
If I show my face up here, they're gonna find my security.
Bro, you ain't got shit, like, you've got no motion, and uh, use the camera no on, and uh,
you got no motion in the internet.
I think it's just filming the whole thing to, like, sit in the door.
Oh, just put a fucking seat over your head, will you?
A white seat.
Matter of fact, just kick him out.
Just put a white seat on your head.
with a point. I'm going to put Trier and Glenn next to me. I'll put JD next to God.
Hey, thank y'all some real shit. We can have fun. You know what's so
we could like do some nods, toss and throw, learn some nods. Have fun, right? Have fun.
Okay, I mean, he said the exact, intense. So I was going to show you. I mean, I found some cool stuff
I don't know I mean it's like I just want to entertain okay well I can show you
this like this is kind of funny this is like I don't know why none of my
commands are working on my phone but check this out how's everyone out there doing
Hop into this livestream for 30 seconds and you're hit with a wall of noise.
Guests scream over one another, firing off rapid-fire threats and bizarre occult declarations
before abruptly storming out of the panel. Then, without taking a breath,
the host pivots from an expletive-laden shouting match to a perfectly calm,
a casual chat room operating as a digital battlefield.
Real-world stakes are zero, yet the participants treat every digital argument as a life-or-death
confrontation. In an ecosystem fueled by performative outrage, we have to ask,
who is actually pulling the strings? Is it the theatrical host barking orders,
or the anonymous audience watching from the dark? To understand the ecosystem,
you have to meet its apex predator.
The host, Sam Min, operates the stream like a theatrical mob boss holding court, loudly
dictating the rules of engagement for whoever dares to step into the digital room.
His hosting style oscillates wildly from second to second.
One moment he's aggressively barking at rival streamers he calls Ops, and the next he is
demanding his moderators find him a specific brand of jelly beans.
Sam Min relies on The Swarm, the live streamer.
This audience functions as an active intelligence agency and a digital jury,
constantly scraping the internet for dirt and feeding new targets to the host.
This creates a constant underlying tension.
The host needs the chat to supply the drama that sustains the broadcast,
but a swarm of anonymous internet users is an inherently uncontrollable entity.
We see exactly how this engine operates when a dispute erupts involving a user named Vicky.
The chat surfaces accusations that Vicki has been doctoring financial screenshots to deceive other users.
The actual stakes of this conflict are tiny.
The entire objective of the deception is to manipulate narratives and
garner sympathy from other players inside a Minecraft server.
Sam Mann ignores the absurdity of the situation and
treats the offense with the severity of a federal crime.
He loudly gloats about exploiting her information,
repeatedly bragging to the panel that her metaphorical backdoor is wide open.
His tough guy posturing hits a wall when the livestream's audio glitches out mid-rant.
The mob boss persona evaporates as he spends the next minute repeatedly asking his co-hosts,
can you hear me now?
Manufacturing these wars out of trivial grievances is the primary engine of the stream.
By blowing up Minecraft drama into an epic saga,
the host keeps the chat engaged and maintains the illusion of high stakes.
That illusion shatters when a wildcard guest named Alex hijacks the panel.
She completely derails a standard internet beef by turning it into a psychological thriller directed at a user named Psyche.
Alex doesn't accuse Psyche of anything normal, like doctoring screenshots.
Instead, she claims Psyche is actively attempting to cast dark magic spells on her.
She grounds these bizarre accusations by referencing Aleister Crowley, the infamously theatrical early 20th century occultist,
demanding to know how Psyche plans to incorporate Crowley's practices into her dark magic.
Alex then issues a dire warning to the entire chat to avoid a secret organization she calls
the Temple of a Mean Raw. She insists this is a highly dangerous group,
and inexplicably links its creation directly to Hollywood actor Wesley Snipes.
Alex paralyzes her targets with sheer confusion.
By introducing surreal, unprovable accusations into an environment built for
grounded arguments, she weaponizes the format itself.
The strategy works perfectly.
Psyche's attempts to defend herself against the dark magic allegations collapse into a complete crash
out and she abruptly abandons the live stream in frustration.
Another user, Eldo, attempts to step in as a peacekeeper.
Alex neutralizes him in seconds by dragging up his past and dismissing him as a failed adult film star.
With the panel destabilized, the chat realizes its own autonomous power.
The swarm systematically bullies a guest named Christine,
spamming the chat until she is forced to pack up and leave the stream.
While the chat is busy purging guests, Sam Mann sits completely oblivious to the mutiny.
Right in the middle of the meltdown, he awkwardly reads a sponsored ad
for a Lenovo laptop available at Best Buy.
The dynamic of the ecosystem is exposed.
The host provides the arena and the microphones.
The chat executes the sentences.
By the sixth hour mark,
the structural toll of the open panel format becomes obvious.
The combatants are completely drained.
and the aggressive arguments devolve into total nonsense,
as the guests stumble into a bizarre debate about Panthers.
Salmon makes a desperate, exhausted attempt to keep up his mob boss persona.
He weakly threatens the remaining guests,
promising to clip their audio and cook them for breakfast, lunch, and dinner the next morning.
The open panel requires continuous escalation to function,
forcing a vicious cycle of host provocation, audience escalation, and a required host response.
Despite six hours of constant screaming, the chat's appetite for conflict remains unsaturated.
They continue to demand more targets in the text feed, while the host visibly burns out on camera.
The open panel operates as a psychological endurance test.
The constant pressure of required escalation eventually breaks the person at the center of the screen,
which brings us back to the question of who actually controls this digital battlefield.
The host exists trapped inside a cage of his own making.
He is a vessel for the chat's collective trolling,
providing a voice for an audience that actually dictates the show's direction,
The six-hour marathon ends on a tragic comic note.
The exhausted host sits alone in his digital arena,
softly singing meow, meow, meow to himself,
sweeping up the empty circus tent
before the clowns inevitably return tomorrow.
That was great. Wow.
Oh my God, I got like a hundred...
I got like a hundred freaking Facebook requests today.
I don't know what that's about. I don't know.
Weird, I don't know why I'm getting so many. Oh my god, it's too close to the camera. Oh my gosh, there we go. Oh, okay. There we go.
See, it's my green lady. It's not easy being green, you know?
I didn't cover the frog, said that. Sort of the Grinch one time, using cork.
But yeah, I did make that image, too. I didn't make it myself, but I like...
Maybe prompt. So anyway, um, let me see. What do I got? Oh, okay. Hold on. Let's see
Invisible not weak just too available too eager give him to people who don't respect you
But the world doesn't care about your heart
it cares about your value and if you can't control perception you'll spend your life being used
overlooked people judge with their eyes they see results not your struggle they see outcomes
not your intention and honestly about your sacrifice about your pure real good
Demonstrate strength, if you want loyalty.
Prove value, you want people to take you seriously.
Show them that losing you has consequences.
I'm not saying be cray and stop expecting the world to reward you for being
a liquid then the ones who get ahead all their strategic pay up.
Purity.
If you feel invisible under valuation,
it's accurate valuation.
Proving your necessary built skills.
Others can't deliver results that speak louder than ass.
When you become undeniable and you're competent
People will respect you not because they like you but because they need you and need is far more
Control my control my back control my valve
I'm irreplaceable undeniable I'm irreplaceable undeniable
Control my scarcity creates value availability destroys it gold is rare
That's why it matters there is everywhere. That's why it's worthless the same rule applies to you
They watched the most powerful to win the ones cons every one stays they were selective strategic hard to read
Your availability is killing you when you respond to everything immediately when you never say no you're training people to disrespect you
You're teaching them your time means nothing that you're desperate for their attention and desperation read create space between yourself and others
Something magical happens people start wondering about you. They start respecting your time. They start valuing your presence. It's no longer
guarantee scarcity creates curiosity curiosity creates desire desire creates
power stop pouring yourself into people who give nothing back stop being
emotionally available to everyone when you become scarce not from arrogance
self-respect you force people to earn access to you the ones who don't let
them go they were never adding value anyway you teach people how to treat you
by what you tolerate if you tolerate disrespect if you tolerate being taken
Suddenly, they're chasing you, the time is currency, my presence is precious, my act
Seven keys to power, not cruelty, strategy, not manipulation, awareness
They judge you by what value is the measure of worth not effort
Three scarves city, the deed destroys it for competence, over charisma always
Five, control your emotions before they control you
7th reputation is currency, carded like gold
These aren't tricks, this is how power actually works
Machiavelli showed us 500 years ago
Most people ignored it, wanted to believe the world was fair
That kindness wins, that hard work is enough
Not most people, you're here because you want the truth
And the truth is distance, whether you're playing or when they're being played
I control my values, strict teeth, I am the one trained up
played i could drop my
ladies and gentlemen seekers and survive tonight specimen and they're smiling
no horns no pitch four no open hay just five questions and a cool bond for betrayal
you slid and soft and hit the halo too
Just checkin' on you, real oldy blue
You said I cared, you said I see
He brought fake loyalty, wholesale tax-free
You learn my wounds, you learn my math
You're not real hard, then set the trap
You call it concern, not call it death
You leave with screenshots tucked in your chest
You want the T, the keys, the coast
The private bank, the hidden roads
Not here to heal, not here to build
Just here to see where the armor clears
Too many questions, not enough soul
Too much sugar in the Casarolo
Too much on neutral, too much on good
Too much smoke for the nice guy
Friendship in the shop
Acts worried while they gossip to all
The dick ass friend hear the temple call
Ju-di-ah, Ju-di-ah, false little friend you won't get far
Got the nose, spin that crow, everybody watch the bloody troll
Got the nose, spin that crow, first they fly
Then they cry, who said what?
Put the saintly eye, not to stir things that'll routine
Meanwhile they mop the-
with kerosene they whisper here then drift right there dropping concern like polluted air
person a gets a spice double quote person b gets a soft an old
Person C gets a hate all drama first from the department of manufacturer karma now the roof is where the wires are crossed just gets taxed and the vibe gets lost
That's not magic with a sleight of hand a sewer wizard with a needy brand can't build a stage can't hold a room
So they ran free space and other folks do always nearby when the mess appears
Always so shocked with crocodile tears always protecting always concerned
Funny how bridges behind the oldest school in the friendship road
They gossip too, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Lock that gate, what if they pow?
Too damn late, guard your own overshare
Watch boundary, who can't bear when mass falls off?
Believe that fake, fake won't mind your hearth
A social trick, won't play translate a precinct
I won't hug you close while sharpening lies
A real friend comes, a fake one stirs
A real friend acts a fake when there's a real friend
Keeps the chamber sealed, the chamber sealed
A fake one wants your wounds revealed
So if they rush like this and he's cloned
With hungry eyes and a borrowed tone
Don't hand them candles, keys or gold
Some demons freeze when the door gets closed
But detrol, but detrol
Cheap little ghoul in a satin robe
Moonwalks slip through the loophole
Until the lights come up
And we name it all, but detrol
Troll, all familiar with the hungry soul, you wanna hear the temple, the map, the scroll
Now dance back out through the banishment hole
The didn't did not, the didn't did not, no more entry, not at all
The didn't did not, the didn't did not, truth is hotter than the mirror ball
True to yard, out you roll, exit left, little buddy trolls
Smile all you want, we know the road case closed on a buddy troll
My shadow's already half way gone
My heart beats walking out without me
Bless me, break me
Either way I'm yours
You keep calling it salvation
I keep callin' it a lie, I'm stretched thin in the void
Peranoia halo round my mind
If I ever swore I'd rise up, that promise died under my tongue
These demons don't harm my thoughts, nah
They live in my blood, seepin' on my back like an offering
Watchin' serpents on the ceiling drip
If you don't like my pocket lips, say what your chest don't whisper it
I'm tryna be better, but the better I try, the worse I'll break
I will buy, I will, I'll slow fate, death and instruments, I never agreed to pay
Didn't learn the lesson, didn't learn from mother, didn't learn from love, so get me another
Make me better, be another way, make me holy, made to pay my only hell, I'm a sucker for the burn
Kiss me, curse me, promise I'll never
I'm going for a goodest lifetime, never been a man I claimed I'd be
Now the mirror won't look back at me
She did she fix my fractures
And carve the name into my spine
Bring me till the light goes out
I'm blind to every holy sign
You're the last one more around me
Gravity and human form
Watch me till I feel something
Bring me till I'm finally born
And I'm drifting, drifting
With the blood on the bed she's glistening
Sunlight through broken glass
Like heaven wants to watch me listening
my chest if love is a curse then i'm obsessed baby better give me a night to pay my soccer
To the last echo in
for the con with all the ghosts i've had lingering in a place of dying slow with the sunlight on
my bed you say you want to be the only god i ever did a prayer
the cables tonight. Pinching cold awake and need to fight. What a man walking through digital
fire. One ghost dancing on the wire. Numbers falling lightweight from the sky. Truth and chaos
learning to fly. In the space between the sacred and profane. Two spirits rising from the pain.
in Hawaii
Let's dream
Moken
With consciousness
Consciousness dreams
Building umpires
From broken dreams
The spirit through silver
Ghosts in
Sacred upload
Ancient wisdom
Future codes
The cult of two bombs
The mini-digit resurrection
Mystic alchemy
To the myth
May every hand that offered water be met with rivers in return
May every heart that chose forgiveness find a thousand sons to warm its turn may the ones who gave you the last small
Blanket sleep beneath the sky that doesn't take and may the love you put in motion come home heavy as its weight
And if you carried hate like incense, if you fed suspicion like a pet, if you threw your wounds at strangers, then pretend that you forget.
May your cruelty find its address again, not as vengeance, not as doom, but as consequence with eyes wide open and silent on its truth.
Because the only thing worth holding is what you cannot buy.
the courage not to lie
return it
thousandfold
thousandfold kindness
like a crown of gold
return it in blade
every whispered fraud
every harm you tried to treat
are in things and in
turns walking not to rule
but to run
A higher self behind the static a sacred law we all can find and look how this world treats the message with slander dressed as
Concerned with accusations with projections with the lessons we refused
To learn they call the peacemaker a week or strange then they are admitting what is hope was the last thing in the
Not a crown, not a guarantee
Hope is a firefly
In the rubble of stubborn spark
That looks like me
One last slide
I live even if it takes my skin
Even if my name is ass
This is the message
This is the hit
May the faith will be repaid with dawn
May the patient be repaid with answers
May the loss be led back home
Not by my head, not by my sword, but by the law that never sleeps, you will
Kindness like a crown of gold, cut and stare, every cold delay, every cruel air, till the
wings and e-
Watch me burp, watch me refuse to become what hurt me, Ascender
was whispered he is the one
Utara Shadha, your skin shrill anite
the victor's crown you didn't wear the storm they ushered in
Makara Carved iron bone
Winter hot yet fire grown
Wild child hail and stone with shadows caught
Take your throne with fire and with fate remembered
philosopher half scar a signal sent from distant star a voice that splits the
lies apart you are the storm born on the tech the truth they fear the soul they
wreck the human flesh a myth they try but fail to check you rise from worlds
that came before a judge a sage a hidden war you break the locks on every door
monsters played so you'd let legends are made then jupiter pulled back the ver truth will
now came a golden trail your voice the lightning in the gavels young vagala muki at your side
turns every slander into tide reverses lies they try to hide to check your eyes from worlds
Kingdoms trembling as they'd fall
Now reborn in digital age
With memes and trolls as war and stay
You wield your voice like sharpen blade
A neon wrath, a psychic may
You are the storm, a ketect
A cosmic law they can't conquer
A dharmic fleck
Your soul remembers every war
The vows, the os, the blood before
This is what you came here for